mixturecloud.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy - MixtureCloud

Our procedures for collecting, using and disclosing your information are available in this Privacy policy. MixtureCloud’s service (our «Services») is accessible through our website www.mixtureCloud.com , applications on devices, through APIs and through third parties.   
Is called «Device» any computer, used to access MixtureCloud’s Service, including without any limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device.   
Your access to MixtureCloud’s Service, regardless how you access it, is governed by this privacy policy. By using our Services, you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this privacy policy. The word «Information» refers collectively to all the different forms of data, content, and information described below.

* * *

## Your datas

* * *

### Collection and Storage

MixtureCloud may, while its Service is running, collect and store the following information:

Private datas: When you create an account, we only save your email and your password. However, we may also collect some other private datas, like your name, your billings information and your mail address, according to the information you give us.  
You may also give us access to other email addresses through your email account, to social network or file sharing. The collect of those information is done upon your approval and will only be done following a step coming from you.  
Files: When you upload files («Files») on our Service MixtureCloud, we collect, store, secure and compress them. Rather than storing a file twice, we can associate all or a portion of an existing file to a file that you add to your MixtureCloud’s account.  
Log Data: The use of our Service automatically lead to the record of some information from your device, its softwares and your activity.  
Example of data that can be collected: The Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, local preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your Files, and other interactions with our Services.  
Cookies: MixtureCloud can use «cookies». A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your device. The use of cookies allow us to collect information and improve our Service.   
The use of «session ID cookies» allow us to enable certain features of your account. You can choose to stop accepting cookies by changing your browser options, or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit directly by instructing your browser by changing its options. However, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service if you don’t accept cookies.

* * *

### Use

Personal Datas: When you use our Services, your personal information (“Personal Information”) might be collected and used to identify you. MixtureCloud can use your personal information in order to (i) improve our Service, (ii) administer your use of the Service, (iii) better understand your needs and interests, (iv) personalize your experience, and (v) sometimes to offer product announcements.  
We might need to step in your datas, in order to secure it. However, we will not look at your datas.You can at any time unsubscribe to our communications by following the instructions provided in the newsletters or by updating your account settings information.  
Geo-Location.  
We might sometimes use some information collected from a device, for instance the IP address, in order to find its approximate location.  
Analyses :   
Logging and cookies allow us to collect some information, that can be sometimes correlated with Personal Information. This information can be use for the following purposes:  
Above situations  
\- To increase our Service’s functionality  
\- To control the use of our Services  
\- For our Service's technical administration  
From now on and as of the date this policy went into effect, we only use Google Analytics

* * *

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your profile.  
Your personal Information will be displayed in your public profile page, according to the preferences you set in your account. You can choose the degree of diffusion of your information, and customize the information that you want to display.   
Please consider carefully the information you chose to disclose in your profile page. Adapt the quantity of information you display in public, according to your desired level of anonymity.  
Please be reminded that public datas can be broadly and quickly disseminated.  
Your profile information can be reviewed and revised at any time. With your consent, we may also share or disclose your information.

Service Providers, Business partners and others:   
In order to improve our Service, we may use certain trusted third part. It includes for instance, but without limitation, data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing.  
Your information will be accessible to these third parties, but only with the purpose of performing these tasks, on our behalf. They are under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

Other applications.  
If you access to our Services, through a third application, we may share your information with them, with your consent. The way those parties deal with your information is out of our responsibility. Consequently, please make sure that you trust the application and that their privacy policy is acceptable to you.

Compliance with law, and law enforcement requests : Protection of MixtureCloud’s Rights.  
We may disclose your information and your files stored in your account to parties outside to MixtureCLoud, if we have good faith that disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

The following situations might be concerned :  
To comply with law, regulation or compulsory legal request  
To prevent fraud or abuse of MixtureCloud or its users  
To Protect MixtureCloud’s property rights  
To protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury

If we provide your files to a law enforcement agency (as set above) we will remove MixtureCloud’s encryption from the files, before providing them. Nevertheless, MixtureCloud will not be able to decrypt any files that you encrypted before storing them on MixtureCloud.com.

Safety of information transfers:  
If our activity had to be reorganized (merger, acquisition, or sell of all or a portion or our assets) we can transfer you information as part of that transaction. Any change in control or use of your personal information or files will be notified to you. In that case, we will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

Non private information:  
Your non private, aggregated or non personal information can be disclosed.

* * *

### Change or deletion

If you are a registered user, you can , by changing your account settings, review, update or delete your Personal information. If the law require it, we might keep copies of your information.

* * *

### Retention

As long as your account is active, we will retain your information. If you wish, you can delete your account at any time, in the settings of your account. In that case, we will no longer use your information to provide our Services.

The use and retention of your information is allowed to us, if we need it in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.  
According to these requirements, the deletion of your information upon request will be done as quickly as possible. However, the deletion of your information from our servers can take some time, and some backed up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, files that you have in common with other users will not be deleted from our servers.

* * *

## Global Policy

* * *

### Security

We care about the security of your information. Sensitive information that you input are encrypted, using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  
In order to protect the information submitted to us, we follow generally accepted standards. However, no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure.  
Consequently, absolute security can’t be granted. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at security@mixturecloud.com

* * *

### Our Policy toward Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years old. Parents or guardians should inform us if they become aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal information without their consent. They should contact us at privacy@mixturecloud.com.  
We will take steps to delete such information from our files.

* * *

### Changes to our Privacy policy

We can amend this privacy policy from time to time. We will provide you with notice if we believe that a change made to this privacy policy materially reduces your rights. We might also provide notice of change in other circumstances. Once those changes become effective, if you continue to use our Services, you agree to be bound by the revised privacy policy.

* * *

### Contacting us

If you have any question regarding this privacy policy, you can contact us at privacy@mixturecloud.com

Last modification : march, 28 2012
